{
    "title": "Movie Quotes Quiz",
    "author": "Chapman Lee",
    "questions": [{
        "question" : "Which famous character was most know for the phrase 'Shanken, not stirred'?",
        "answers" : [	"James Bond",
        				"James T. Kirk",
        				"Sean Connery",
                        "Jedi"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }, {
        "question" : "'I'll be back' was a famous quote by Arnold Schwarzenegger in which film?",
        "answers" : [   "Commando",
                        "Jaws",
                        "The Terminator",
                        "The Terminal"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "'May the Force be with you' is a quote from which movie?",
        "answers" : [   "SpaceBalls",
                        "Taxi Driver",
                        "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial",
                        "Star Wars"],
        "correct_answer" : "3"
    }, {
        "question" : "Which famous quote was from the film The Wizard of OZ",
        "answers" : [   "'There's no business like show business'",
                        "'There's no place like home'",
                        "'Round up the usual suspects"],
        "correct_answer" : "1"
    }, {
        "question" : "'I see dead people' is a quote from which film?",
        "answers" : [   "The Sixth Sense",
                        "Signs",
                        "The Shining"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }, {
        "question" : "Which notable quote was first said in the film Apollo 13 by Tom Hanks",
        "answers" : [   "We rob banks",
                        "Houston, we have a problem",
                        "There's no crying in baseball"],
        "correct_answer" : "1"
    }, {
        "question" : "'My precious' is a quote from which Lord of The Rings character?",
        "answers" : [   "Bilbo Baggins",
                        "Gandalf The White",
                        "Gollum"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "In Titanic what did Jack yell at the front of the boat?",
        "answers" : [   "I'm the king of the world",
                        "I'm Flying",
                        "My heart will go on"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }, {
        "question" : "'Elementary, my dear Watson' is a quote from which character?",
        "answers" : [   "Sherlock Holmes",
                        "Mycroft Holmes",
                        "Irene Adler",
                        "Dr. John Watson"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }, {
        "question" : "Which quote came from the film Casablanca?",
        "answers" : [   "Say 'hello' to my little friend!",
                        "Of all the gin joints in all the towns in all the world, she walks into mine",
                        "As God is my witness, I'll never be hungrey again",
                        "Gentlemen, you can't fight in here! This is a War Room!"],
        "correct_answer" : "1"
    }, {
        "question" : "'Here's Johnny!' is a quote from which movie adaptation of Stephen King's books?",
        "answers" : [   "Carrie",
                        "Cujo",
                        "The Shining",
                        "The Shawshank Redemption"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "Complete the famous quote 'Mrs. Robinson, you're trying to ________ _________. Aren't you?'",
        "answers" : [   "kill me",
                        "rob me",
                        "seduce me"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "'You're gonna need a bigger boat.' is a line from which famous shark related movie?",
        "answers" : [   "Deep Blue Sea",
                        "Sharknado",
                        "Ghost Ship",
                        "Jaws"],
        "correct_answer" : "3"
    }, {
        "question" : "What is Travis Bickle most well know phrase (played by Robert De Niro) in the film Taxi Driver",
        "answers" : [   "You talkin' to me?",
                        "There's no place like home",
                        "Louis, I think this is the begining of a beautiful friendship"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }, {
        "question" : "The phrase 'Go ahead, make my day' was said by which famous actor who played Harry Callahan in Sudden Impact?",
        "answers" : [   "Sean Connery",
                        "Sylvester Stallone",
                        "Clint Eastwood",
                        "Jason Statham"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "Which film did the phrase 'I'm going to make him an offer he can't refuse.' originate from?",
        "answers" : [   "Scarface",
                        "Taxi Driver",
                        "Gran Turino",
                        "The Godfather"],
        "correct_answer" : ""
    }, {
        "question" : "Complete the phrase, '...Bond, _______ Bond.",
        "answers" : [   "Jackie",
                        "Jamie",
                        "James",
                        "John"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "In which comedic film was the phrase 'Surely you can't be serious.' and 'I am serious... and don't call me Shirley' come from?",
        "answers" : [   "Airplane!",
                        "Naked Gun",
                        "Scary Movie"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }, {
        "question" : "In which Robin Williams film was the phrase 'Carpe diem. Seize the day boys. Make your lives extraordinary'?",
        "answers" : [   "Mrs. Doubtfire",
                        "Flubber",
                        "Dead Poets Society"],
        "correct_answer" : "2"
    }, {
        "question" : "During the attack on the Death Star in Star Wars: A New Hope who said the phrase 'Use the force, Luke'?",
        "answers" : [   "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
                        "Darth Vader",
                        "Han Solo",
                        "Mace Windu"],
        "correct_answer" : "0"
    }]
}
